

+44(0)758 273 5926 hong1015.github.io/Portfolio hongwong1015@gmail.com

# PROFILE

My name is Hong, I've been working as a Frontend developer in ZPG since 2015. As time goes on I have faced many challenges and learnt how to overcome them. I have gain extensive experience in building websites and solving many common problems that occur.

I am experienced at HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript as well as basic React, Angular and Backend languages like C#, Razor and .NET. I work well under pressure and always use any spare time to improve myself by developing new

# SKILLS

Html
CSS (LESS)
JavaScript & JQuery
SQL, C# and React
PHP
3D Modeling
2D & 3D Animation
Videos Editing
Photography

# Softwares

Visual Studio, TSF
Microsoft SQL Server
Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Premier Pro
3D Studio Max, Unity
Blender
ZBrush

# **EDUCATION**

Anglia Ruskin University (2009 - 2012) BSc (Hons) Multimedia, Animation and the Web 2:1

The Colne Community School and College A level (2007-2009)

Economics, Information & Communications Technology, AS Chinese, AS Art & Design 8 GCSE's (2002–2007)

# WORKING HISTORY

#### ZPG (January 2015 - Present)

Frontend developer -

Create, modify and maintain template and bespoke websites.

Create HTML email.

Troubleshoot existing websites.

Working with outsource resource in and out of the UK, with website styling and function issues.

Experience working with Razor, Knockout.js, ASP.NET, VB.NET and C# based website. Using SQL for delete or update client database.

Assisting my manger in his absence with work allocation and general management of the development team of 6.

#### Simonleedesign (July 2014)

Website development and image retouching

#### SeymourPowell (May 2014 - Jun 2014)

Responsive website development

# Two Wheels Rider Magazine (Sep 2013)

Logo design

# 2C Company Limited (March 2013 - August 2013)

Junior marketing officer

#### Pacific Union Consultants Ltd. (Jun 2013)

Logo design

# Brentwood Jiu Jitsu Club (Aug 2011 to present) & Anglia Ruskin University Jiu Jitsu Club (Dec 2010 to present)

Website design, development and maintenance

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I am a British Citizen, I can speak, read and write fluent Cantonese, Traditional Chinese and English.

My interests are Boxercise, Kick boxing, Basketball, Brazilian Jiu-jitsu and Jiu jitsu, I was also the university Jiu jitsu club treasurer, website maintainer and part of my role was to help at the university fresher's fair to recruit new members for the club. I am trustworthy, hardworking and self-motivated. My spare time hobbies are gaming, watching movies, exercise, landscape photography, table tennis, catching up with new design trends and learning new skills.